Guide to the Creative Time Archive 1973-2006 MSS.179
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Audio
  - Subseries B: Audio Recordings - Originals
    - 42nd Street Art Project - NPR, 7/8/93 [Press], 1993 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0105)
    - Board Meeting, 9/29/93, 1993 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0082)
    - Norman Salant, "sax/on", "After Ours", 1994 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0059)
    - Julia Meltzer, Amanda Ramos, "Chatlandia, 3 Conversations", [1995] (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0117)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Ben Neill, July 27, [1996] (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0033)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Vernon Reid, July 27, [1996] (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0036)
    - Paco Cao, [1996] (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0009)
      Format: Microcassette
    - Phil Kline, "Winter Music", 12/96, 1996 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0072)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Adrianne Wortzel proposal, 2/25/97, 1997 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0070)
    - Guillermo Gomez-Pena, "El Mexterminator", 1997 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0111)
    - "El Mexterminator", WBAI Voices Against the Wall, 6/5/98 [Press], 1998 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0099)
    - Karen Finley, "A Message from…", 1-900-ALL-KAREN, 2/16/98, 1998 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0089)
    - Karen Finley, "A Message from…", 1-900-ALL-KAREN, 2/16/98, 1998 (Box not specified, Folder ID: 179.0122)
    - Shimon Attie, "Tribute to Joe Papp", 11/1/98, 1998 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0080)
    - CT Interview - Anne Pasternak, 10/09/01, "On WTC response", 2001 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0017)
    - CT Interview - Anne Pasternak, 12/03/01, "General", 2001 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0019)
    - CT Interview - Carol Stakenas, 10/26/01, 2001 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0011)
    - CT Interview - Elizabeth Iarrappino, 11/9/01, 2001 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0001)
    - CT Interview - Kelly Evans, 11/14/01, 2001 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0007)
    - CT Interview - Kevin [McHugh], 11/09/01, 2001 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0021)
    - CT Interview - Prof. Harriet Senie, 11/29/01, 2001 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0005)
    - CT Interview - Rachel Stevens, 11/12/01, 2001 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0013)
    - CT Interview - Sarah Bacon, 11/02/01, 2001 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0015)
    - Memorial Discussion, 3/28/02 (1 of 2), 2002 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0095)
    - Memorial Meeting, NYU, 3/28/02 (1 of 2), 2002 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0096)
    - Anita Contini Interview, Artists' Space, Christian Science Monitor (Cut #4), Undated (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0091)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Closing Party, Tape #1, Undated (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0076)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Closing Party, Tape #2, Undated (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0049)
    - Calvin Trillin, Undated (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0113)
    - Karen Tape, Undated (Box not specified, Folder ID: 179.0003)
    - NEA Music Tape Copy, Undated (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0045)
- Series VII: Mail Art - Marcos Kurtycz
  This series consists of various mailed objects created by artist Marcos Kurtycz including postcards, correspondence, books, performance and exhibition flyers, posters, and many art objects sent between 1988 and 1990 to Debbie Levine and Cee Scott Brown of Creative Time. Additional mailed objects from Kurtycz may be found in Oversize Series.
  - Misc. Kurtycz Exhibition/Performance cards, 1979,1989,1989 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Clipping - "Accion al Mediodia" performance photo montage, Chapultepec, Mexico, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - "Mira" book by Marcos Kurtycz and Anna Kutycz, 15 May 1987 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Misc. Envelopes, addressed to Cee Brown and Debbie Levine, Creative Time [5 items], 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - "Fuegomar" performance documentation booklet by Kurtycz, February 1988 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - "Taller de Juguete Magico" art proposal book by Kurtycz, 16 March 1988 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - "Zero Village" stamped sheets with envelope, 30 June 1988 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - "Zero Village" performance flyers, Yellow Springs Institute, 16 July 1988 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Yellow Springs Institute program information, Kurtycz residency acceptance letter, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - August 1988 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - "Do You Know Hockers?" book by Kurtycz, for Kurtix' Softwars Matrix, August 1988 [2 copies] (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - "Hocker" printed tablecloth - "The Morning After Therapy", 11 December 1988 (Box 23)
  - "Hocker" sheets, for Kurtix' Softwars Matrix, August 1988 [8 unique sheets] (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - September 1988 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Envelopes - October 1988 [7 items] (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - October 1988 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 7 October 1988 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 13 October 1988 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 13 October 1988 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 13 October 1988 [not postmarked] (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Lead [metal] "Hocker" artwork with note, 20 October 1988 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 24 October 1988 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 24 October 1988 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - "Organikwars" flyers [for Creative Time performance] with letter, 26 October 1988 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Envelopes - November 1988 [10 items] (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Postcard(s) - "Softwars Cardpost", 3 November 1988 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 5 November 1988 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Misc. flyers - "Up Tiempo", "Softwars", "Preempting Swarm", etc., stamped 5 November 1988 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 7 November 1988 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 7 November 1988 [not postmarked] (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 9 November 1988 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 9 November 1988 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Postcard - 14 November 1988 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 21 November 1988 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 22 November 1988 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Postcard - 24 November 1988 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - "Tercera Gracia de Via Angelina" prints, 24 November 1988 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 28 November 1988 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", November 1988 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - "Artforum Bombing Action" performance booklet (San Diego, CA, 1985), mailed November 1988 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Misc. Mail Art - November 1988 [4 items] (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Mail Art - "Organikwars Triptych", December 1988 [not postmarked] (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - "Heart of Calm" (poem by Kim Niemala Duggan) assorted flyers for "Organikwars Triptych", December 1988 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - "Border+ing Manual" book by Kurtycz, "Softwars Editions", 1988 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Envelope - February 1989 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence - February 1989 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - "Island Discovery" book by Kurtycz for "NYPR89EKT", with letter to Martha Wilson, 14 February 1989 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Postcard - 7 March 1989 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence - "Biheaded Island", 17 March 1989 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence - 19 March 1989 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Postcard - "NYPR89EKT", March 1989 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence - 4 April 1989 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost", 24 June 1989 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Envelope - 8 July 1989 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - "Butterfny" prototypes, "NYPR89EKT" [2 unique items], 1989 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - "Reverse Degrading" artwork, "NYPR89EKT", 1989 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - "Reverse Degrading" artwork, "NYPR89EKT", Creekwood Editions, January 1989 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Misc. "NYPR89EKT" artwork [7 items], 1989 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - "Rumi's Room" booklet by Kurtycz, edited for Softwars Matrix, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Envelope - December 1990 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Misc. "XYZOMPANTLI" performance materials, with note to Cee Brown, 17 December 1990 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Misc. Mail Art - "Organikwars" [not postmarked], Undated (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Misc. Mail Art - "Organikwars" [not postmarked] [3 items], Undated (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Postcard - "Softwars Cardpost" [not postmarked], Undated (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - Postcard - "Software Cardpost" [not postmarked], Undated (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - "El Labertinto de Kurtycz" book by Kurtycz [2 items], Undated (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - "Maiz" book by Kurtycz, Guaytalpa Editions, Undated (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - "Mi Casa" book by Kurtycz, Softwars MacroMex Editions [3 items], Undated (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Lead [metal] "Hocker" artwork with note, Undated (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - "Agrest" artwork, Undated (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - Misc. untitled artworks [5 items], Undated (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - "Laurie Anderson for Softwars Organikwars" sheets, Undated (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Misc. untitled faces print, Undated (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - "Organikwars Hockers" stamped images [7 unique sheets], Undated (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - "Organikwars Topsy-Turvy Hocker" artwork, Undated (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - "The Wheel" artworks, "Organikwars" [2 unique items], Undated (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - "Organikwars" faces folded print, Undated (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - "Organikwars Hocker" card, Undated (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - "Organikwars Editor Hocker" artwork, Undated (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - "Organikwars Editor" artwork, Undated (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - Postcard - "C'Mamoth", "Softwars Cardpost" [not postmarked], Undated (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - "Organikwars: Limited Up Tiempo" folded print, Undated (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - "Grinding of Hockers" stamped page, Undated (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - "Oftenly, it's painful to be a Hocker" print, Undated (Box 20, Folder 83)
  - "Glorious 88", Softwars MacroMex Editions, Undated (Box 20, Folder 84)
  - Photograph - Kurtycz working on roof, Undated (Box 20, Folder 85)
  - Sticker sheets - "Hocker"; "NYPR89EKT", Undated (Box 20, Folder 86)
  - Paper Bag - "Organikwars Hocker", Undated (Box 20, Folder 87)
  - Envelopes - "Taller Visual" [not postmarked], Undated (Box 20, Folder 88)
  - Mirror with Photo artwork, Undated (Box 20, Folder 89)
- Oversize Series
  This series contains oversize materials from Series I, IV, VII and includes exhibition catalogues, magazines, building proposals, photographic materials (including negatives, contact sheets, and prints), blueprints, posters, and hand-drawn mock-ups for exhibition catalogue.
  - Oversize Series I: Projects, Programs and Publications
    - Janet Kardon and Paula Marincola, "Red Grooms' Philadelphia Cornucopia" (Institute of Contemporary Art, University of Pennsylvania, 1982) (Box 21, Folder 258)
    - Stroll magazine, Vol. 1, No. 1 (Spring/Summer, 1985) (Box 21, Folder 259)
    - "Fragments From the Journals of Charles Cooper", intro. Jane Greengold ("A Drop in the Bucket"), 1985 (Box 21, Folder 260)
    - Stroll magazine, Vol. 2, No. 1 (Winter, 1986) [Art on the Beach feature] (Box 21, Folder 261)
    - Stroll magazine, Vol. 2, No. 2 (Nov-Jan, 1986) (Box 21, Folder 262)
    - "Honeymoon Miralda Project, 1986-1992" (Barcelona, Spain: Ambit Serveis Editorials, 1988) [2 copies] (Box 21, Folder 263)
    - Performance in the Park 1986-1987 catalogue [2 copies] (Box 21, Folder 264)
    - Battery Maritime Building Proposals - Diller and Scofidio architectural proposal; CT and Dance Theater Workshop proposal [2 items], 1988 (Box 21, Folder 265)
    - Poster - Art on the Beach, 1978 (Folder 5 Right)
    - Autograph Mock-Ups for exhibition catalogue [2 sheets] - Custom and Culture, 1979 (Folder 6 Right)
    - Blueprints - Art on the Beach, Craig S. Konyk, Eric Gould, Anthony Tsirantonakis, Jim Croak, Ken Kaplan, Ted Krueger [12 items], 1987 (Folder 12)
    - Poster - "Kissing Doesn't Kill: Greed and Indifference Do", Gran Fury, [1989] (Folder 1 Left)
    - Posters - "Surgeon General's Warning", Beth B. [5 items], 1990 (Folder 13)
    - Blueprints - "Sacrificial Ornament", Spring Hurlbut [3 items], 1991 (Folder 11)
    - Poster - "Visualize This", Nancy Burson, [1991] (Folder 4 Left)
    - Posters - Art on the Beach [2 items], Undated (Folder 3 Left)
    - Posters - Art on the Beach [2 items], Undated (Folder 2 Left)
    - Poster - Art in the Anchorage, Undated (Folder 9 Right)
    - Facsimiles, undated (Folder 1, Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6)
  - Oversize Series VII: Marcos Kurtycz - Mail Art
    - Envelope art - fold-out faces print, 25 November 1988 (Folder 7 Right)
    - Envelope art - "Southwestern Fires", 1988 (Folder 10 Right)
    - "XYZOMPANTLI" performance poster, 8 December 1990 (Folder 8 Right)
    - "Organikwars Hocker" fold-out artwork, Undated (Folder 14)